[
{"text": ["Mullica", "Hill", ",", "New", "Jersey"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Hymenolepis", "diminuta", "''", "—", "in", "humans"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Villeneuve", ",", "Fribourg"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Coffs", "Harbour", ",", "New", "South", "Wales"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["RM", "of", "St.", "Clements"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["He", "is", "from", "Andhra", "Pradesh", "in", "South", "India", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["After", "carrying", "boats", "to", "the", "Philippines", "in", "August", ",", "''Cabildo", "''", "reported", "in", "Wakanoura", "Wan", ",", "Honshū", ",", "on", "11", "September", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["This", "species", "is", "only", "found", "in", "the", "Caribbean", "Sea", ",", "where", "it", "is", "abundant", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "Nebria", "orientalis", "''", "Banninger", ",", "1949"], "label": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Barvish", "Kani", ",", "Nanur"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["''", "Perlamantis", "allibertii", "''"], "label": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["North", "Western", "Reform", "Synagogue", ",", "Golders", "Green"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Jersey", "Shore", "Shark", "Attack", "''"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["``", "The", "Cost", "of", "Capital", ",", "Corporation", "Finance", "and", "the", "Theory", "of", "Investment", "''", "(", "1958", ")", ",", "by", "Franco", "Modigliani", "and", "Merton", "Miller", "."], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["Commonwealth", "Stadium", ",", "Lexington", ",", "Kentucky"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Network", "Television", "Marketing", "(", "Replaced", "by", "Shalimar", "Television", "Network", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["List", "of", "schools", "in", "Queensland"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Premier", "League", "of", "Belize", "''", "'", "''", "6", "clubs", "''"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["lawyer", ",", "member", "of", "July", "20", "Plot"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Storyline", "''", "(", "2014", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["84th", "Radar", "Evaluation", "Squadron"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["The", "Legendary", "Fok", "''", "大俠霍元甲"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Beside", "You", "in", "Time"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["For", "this", "duty", "he", "was", "awarded", "the", "Navy", "Cross", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["St", "Peter", "'s", "College", ",", "Gampaha"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["''Lenin", "in", "Kremlin", "''", ",", "by", "Nikolai", "Baskakov"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Taluk", "/", "Tehsil", ":", "Taliparamba"], "label": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Shanna", "Zolman", "(", "2006–2007", ",", "2009", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Lau", "Kong", "as", "Ye-lut", "Hung-kei"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["My", "Little", "Pony", "(", "TV", "series", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["He", "married", "Edith", "Mason", "in", "1919", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Eugenie", "Bouchard", "Svetlana", "Kuznetsova", "Lucie", "Šafářová", "Agnieszka", "Radwańska"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Thomas", "A.", "Saunders", "III"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Joakim", "Noah", "(", "13", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Don", "Ryder", ",", "Baron", "Ryder", "of", "Eaton", "Hastings"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Floyd", "McKissick", ",", "Jr", "."], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Constantine", "Phipps", ",", "1st", "Marquess", "of", "Normanby"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Len", "Braund", "(", "1901–1907", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Eureeka", "'s", "Castle", "''"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["Steve", "Roach", "(", "musician", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Owl", "Eyes", "–", "``", "Pumped", "Up", "Kicks", "''", "(", "Foster", "the", "People", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["Mehmed", "Janjoš", "(", "Oct", "18", ",", "2010", "–", "Aug", "15", ",", "2011", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Richard", "Fuller", "(", "environmentalist", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
]