[
{"text": ["Yao", ",", "Osaka"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["He", "died", "in", "1970", "in", "Miami", "Beach", ",", "Florida", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["The", "damage", "necessitated", "a", "return", "to", "Pearl", "Harbor", "for", "repairs", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Abydos", ",", "Egypt"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Life", "...", "But", "How", "To", "Live", "It", "?"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["The", "Phone", "Co-op"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["LSG", "Sky", "Chefs"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Graham", "Fitkin", "(", "born", "1963", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": [")", "have", "been", "conjectured", "as", "``", "Tiberius", "''", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": [":", "Joe", "Pantalone", "-", "3,251"], "label": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Prominent", "students", "included", "William", "James", "Mayo", "and", "Charles", "Horace", "Mayo", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
]