[
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "1984",
      ",",
      "he",
      "produced",
      "the",
      "talking",
      "heads",
      "concert",
      "film",
      "stop",
      "making",
      "sense",
      "with",
      "director",
      "jonathan",
      "demme",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "desperado",
      "features",
      "additional",
      "background",
      "vocals",
      "by",
      "james",
      "fauntleroy",
      "ii",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "bhumibol",
      "performed",
      "with",
      "preservation",
      "hall",
      "jazz",
      "band",
      ",",
      "benny",
      "goodman",
      ",",
      "stan",
      "getz",
      ",",
      "lionel",
      "hampton",
      ",",
      "and",
      "benny",
      "carter",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "2015",
      ",",
      "olivia",
      "holt",
      "performed",
      "a",
      "cover",
      "of",
      "the",
      "song",
      "on",
      "the",
      "series",
      "finale",
      "of",
      "i",
      "didn't",
      "do",
      "it",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "replaced",
      "starting",
      "pitcher",
      "jamie",
      "brown",
      "on",
      "the",
      "roster"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "stieg",
      "larsson",
      "—",
      "the",
      "girl",
      "with",
      "the",
      "dragon",
      "tattoo",
      ",",
      "the",
      "girl",
      "who",
      "played",
      "with",
      "fire",
      ",",
      "and",
      "the",
      "girl",
      "who",
      "kicked",
      "the",
      "hornets'",
      "nest"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "danses",
      "concertantes",
      "is",
      "a",
      "work",
      "for",
      "chamber",
      "orchestra",
      "by",
      "igor",
      "stravinsky",
      ",",
      "composed",
      "in",
      "1942",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "show",
      "was",
      "written",
      "by",
      "and",
      "starred",
      "niall",
      "tóibín",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "cnn",
      "anchor",
      "lou",
      "dobbs",
      "devoted",
      "more",
      "than",
      "one",
      "hundred",
      "broadcast",
      "segments",
      "to",
      "the",
      "case",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "michael",
      "bay",
      "(",
      "film",
      "director",
      "known",
      "for",
      "high",
      "budget",
      "action",
      "films",
      ")"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "national",
      "champions",
      "were",
      "club",
      "universitario",
      "de",
      "deportes",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "morgan",
      "was",
      "selected",
      "to",
      "receive",
      "a",
      "sloan",
      "fellows",
      "program",
      "to",
      "prepare",
      "her",
      "for",
      "a",
      "management",
      "position",
      "at",
      "the",
      "space",
      "center",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "his",
      "film",
      "trace",
      "of",
      "stones",
      "was",
      "banned",
      "for",
      "20",
      "years",
      "in",
      "1966",
      "by",
      "the",
      "ruling",
      "socialist",
      "unity",
      "party",
      "of",
      "germany",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "(",
      "bachelor",
      "of",
      "law",
      ")",
      "degrees",
      "from",
      "the",
      "university",
      "of",
      "karachi",
      "in",
      "1976",
      "and",
      "1981",
      ",",
      "respectively",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "is",
      "currently",
      "used",
      "by",
      "both",
      "the",
      "army",
      "and",
      "air",
      "force",
      "of",
      "austria",
      ",",
      "germany",
      ",",
      "switzerland",
      ",",
      "denmark",
      ",",
      "and",
      "norway",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "boller",
      "was",
      "the",
      "defensive",
      "line",
      "coach",
      "for",
      "the",
      "dallas",
      "cowboys",
      "of",
      "the",
      "national",
      "football",
      "league",
      "(",
      "nfl",
      ")",
      "from",
      "1996",
      "to",
      "1997",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "laurie",
      "'s",
      "early",
      "films",
      "included",
      "juno",
      "and",
      "the",
      "paycock",
      ",",
      "directed",
      "by",
      "alfred",
      "hitchcock",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "battleship",
      "–",
      "design",
      "of",
      "ships",
      "and",
      "weapons"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "rawhide",
      "(",
      "only",
      "for",
      "seven",
      "seasons",
      "from",
      "1959",
      "until",
      "1965",
      ")"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "wally",
      "wood",
      "published",
      "witzend",
      "in",
      "1966",
      ",",
      "soon",
      "passing",
      "the",
      "title",
      "on",
      "to",
      "artist",
      "editor",
      "bill",
      "pearson",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "codex",
      "contains",
      "the",
      "text",
      "of",
      "the",
      "four",
      "gospel",
      "on",
      "289",
      "parchment",
      "leaves",
      "(",
      "size",
      ")",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "today",
      "it",
      "serves",
      "as",
      "a",
      "center",
      "of",
      "contemporary",
      "art",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "movie",
      "traffic",
      "explores",
      "both",
      "sides",
      "of",
      "this",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "various",
      "international",
      "films",
      "were",
      "screened",
      "to",
      "promote",
      "cinematic",
      "art",
      "and",
      "film",
      "appreciation",
      "in",
      "thailand",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "is",
      "a",
      "tributary",
      "of",
      "the",
      "meramec",
      "river",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "hacıköy",
      "is",
      "a",
      "village",
      "in",
      "the",
      "gölpazarı",
      ",",
      "bilecik",
      "province",
      ",",
      "turkey",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "ackerman",
      "was",
      "educated",
      "at",
      "secondary",
      "school",
      "level",
      "in",
      "andernach",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "she",
      "dies",
      "that",
      "night",
      ",",
      "and",
      "on",
      "the",
      "same",
      "night",
      "her",
      "son",
      "is",
      "shot",
      "in",
      "morbihan",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "2005",
      ":",
      "the",
      "forgotten",
      "arm",
      "(",
      "v2",
      ")",
      "bass",
      ",",
      "backing",
      "vocals"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "championship",
      "game",
      "was",
      "broadcast",
      "on",
      "espn+",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "this",
      "is",
      "a",
      "list",
      "of",
      "vehicles",
      "made",
      "by",
      "chevrolet",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "2004",
      ",",
      "they",
      "created",
      "a",
      "myspace",
      "profile",
      ",",
      "posted",
      "songs",
      "online",
      ",",
      "and",
      "immediately",
      "began",
      "to",
      "connect",
      "with",
      "several",
      "worldwide",
      "fans",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "cbs",
      "charged",
      "$",
      "5.25",
      "million",
      "for",
      "each",
      "30",
      "second",
      "advertisement",
      "that",
      "aired",
      "during",
      "the",
      "game",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "served",
      "as",
      "a",
      "musician",
      "and",
      "musical",
      "director",
      "for",
      "a",
      "number",
      "of",
      "years",
      "for",
      "royal",
      "caribbean",
      "international",
      "performing",
      "in",
      "over",
      "fifty",
      "countries",
      "on",
      "six",
      "continents",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "was",
      "discovered",
      "in",
      "1958",
      "and",
      "developed",
      "by",
      "omv",
      "petrom",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "organisation",
      "functions",
      "as",
      "a",
      "nonprofit",
      "organization",
      "worker",
      "cooperative",
      "where",
      "profits",
      "are",
      "split",
      "50",
      "/",
      "50",
      "between",
      "author",
      "and",
      "publisher",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "a",
      "seasoned",
      "pan",
      "should",
      "not",
      "be",
      "placed",
      "in",
      "a",
      "conventional",
      "dishwasher",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "usage",
      "of",
      "pen",
      "involves",
      "two",
      "types",
      ",",
      "one",
      "for",
      "drawing",
      "made",
      "from",
      "bambusoideae",
      ",",
      "the",
      "other",
      "for",
      "drawing",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "preparation",
      "of",
      "cajun",
      "/",
      "creole",
      "dishes",
      "such",
      "as",
      "crawfish",
      "étouffée",
      ",",
      "gumbo",
      ",",
      "and",
      "jambalaya",
      "all",
      "start",
      "from",
      "this",
      "base",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "loans",
      "had",
      "been",
      "made",
      "on",
      "a",
      "revolving",
      "credit",
      "agreement",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "design",
      "of",
      "the",
      "steering",
      "wheel",
      ",",
      "reminiscent",
      "of",
      "the",
      "porsche",
      "356",
      ",",
      "ensured",
      "minimal",
      "disruption",
      "of",
      "the",
      "view",
      "of",
      "the",
      "instruments",
      "behind",
      "it",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "real",
      "money",
      "for",
      "designers",
      "lie",
      "within",
      "perfume",
      "and",
      "handbags",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "some",
      "recipes",
      "require",
      "up",
      "to",
      "thirty",
      "main",
      "ingredients",
      "and",
      "twelve",
      "condiment",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "company",
      "'s",
      "primary",
      "focus",
      "is",
      "praline",
      "(",
      "chocolate",
      "shells",
      "with",
      "soft",
      "fillings",
      ")",
      ",",
      "but",
      "they",
      "also",
      "sell",
      "marzipan",
      ",",
      "solid",
      "chocolates",
      ",",
      "and",
      "other",
      "confectionery",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  }
]