[
  {
    "text": [
      "joe",
      "satriani",
      "–",
      "guitar",
      "solo",
      "(",
      "track",
      "7",
      ")"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "bryan",
      "sutton",
      "banjo",
      ",",
      "acoustic",
      "guitar",
      ",",
      "mandolin"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "later",
      "became",
      "the",
      "paper",
      "'s",
      "miami",
      "bureau",
      "chief",
      "prior",
      "to",
      "elián",
      "gonzález",
      "brotons",
      "arrival",
      "and",
      "the",
      "international",
      "controversy",
      "surrounding",
      "the",
      "cubans",
      "boy",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "life",
      "masks",
      "of",
      "elizabeth",
      "taylor",
      "and",
      "richard",
      "burton",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "li",
      "xiaolu",
      "&",
      "ma",
      "jian",
      "as",
      "vendors",
      "selling",
      "counterfeits"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "some",
      "opponents",
      ",",
      "including",
      "herminio",
      "iglesias",
      ",",
      "called",
      "for",
      "voters",
      "to",
      "participate",
      "in",
      "the",
      "referendum",
      "and",
      "vote",
      "against",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "donald",
      "meets",
      "ivana",
      "trump",
      "and",
      "the",
      "two",
      "get",
      "married",
      ",",
      "despite",
      "her",
      "initial",
      "reluctance",
      "to",
      "sign",
      "a",
      "prenuptial",
      "agreement",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "old",
      "cathedral",
      ",",
      "painted",
      "in",
      "1802",
      "by",
      "william",
      "crotch"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "2015",
      "–",
      "(",
      "mex",
      ")",
      "el",
      "que",
      "le",
      "bajó",
      "la",
      "novia",
      "a",
      "luismi",
      "for",
      "the",
      "revenant",
      "†"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "jack",
      "lemmon",
      "directed",
      "the",
      "film",
      ",",
      "kotch",
      ",",
      "starring",
      "walter",
      "matthau",
      ",",
      "deborah",
      "winters",
      ",",
      "felicia",
      "farr",
      ",",
      "charles",
      "aidman",
      ",",
      "and",
      "ellen",
      "geer",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "film",
      ",",
      "birds",
      "can",
      "feature",
      "as",
      "the",
      "major",
      "driving",
      "force",
      "in",
      "a",
      "story",
      ",",
      "as",
      "in",
      "alfred",
      "hitchcock",
      "acclaimed",
      "1963",
      "the",
      "birds",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "after",
      "the",
      "association",
      "of",
      "the",
      "two",
      "newspapers",
      ",",
      "léon",
      "nicole",
      "served",
      "as",
      "their",
      "editor",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "she",
      "is",
      "married",
      "to",
      "harish",
      "khare",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "2002",
      "–",
      "odd",
      "børretzen",
      ",",
      "humorist",
      "and",
      "satirist"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "chuck",
      "ainlay",
      "–",
      "recording",
      "(",
      "1",
      ",",
      "3",
      ",",
      "4",
      ",",
      "7",
      "11",
      ")",
      ",",
      "mixing",
      "(",
      "3",
      ",",
      "6",
      ",",
      "8",
      ",",
      "11",
      ",",
      "12",
      ")"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "boyd",
      "approached",
      "manfred",
      "mann",
      "singer",
      "paul",
      "jones",
      "and",
      "suggested",
      "that",
      "they",
      "put",
      "one",
      "together",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "wedding",
      "was",
      "attended",
      "by",
      "paula",
      "echevarría",
      "and",
      "cecilia",
      "freire",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "annually",
      ",",
      "the",
      "institute",
      "receives",
      "us",
      "$",
      "20",
      "million",
      "from",
      "the",
      "government",
      "of",
      "india",
      "and",
      "world",
      "bank",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "at",
      "the",
      "conclusion",
      "of",
      "the",
      "series",
      ",",
      "they",
      "continued",
      "to",
      "perform",
      "together",
      "and",
      "released",
      "three",
      "studio",
      "albums",
      "as",
      "the",
      "boy",
      "band",
      "f4",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "B-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "fimleikafélag",
      "hafnarfjarðar",
      "was",
      "drawn",
      "against",
      "glenavon",
      "f.c.",
      "from",
      "northern",
      "ireland",
      "in",
      "round",
      "1",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "laurer",
      "and",
      "sean",
      "waltman",
      "approached",
      "red",
      "light",
      "district",
      "video",
      "to",
      "distribute",
      "the",
      "homemade",
      "video",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "during",
      "the",
      "1919",
      "and",
      "1920",
      "seasons",
      ",",
      "he",
      "played",
      "for",
      "the",
      "portland",
      "beavers",
      "in",
      "the",
      "pacific",
      "coast",
      "league",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "she",
      "has",
      "been",
      "a",
      "member",
      "of",
      "europe",
      "ecology",
      "–",
      "the",
      "greens",
      "(",
      "eelv",
      ")",
      "since",
      "2013",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "other",
      "shops",
      "in",
      "the",
      "square",
      "are",
      "oxfam",
      ",",
      "carphone",
      "warehouse",
      "and",
      "costa",
      "coffee",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "the",
      "year",
      "1906",
      "he",
      "became",
      "a",
      "member",
      "of",
      "the",
      "(",
      "an",
      "association",
      "of",
      "libertines",
      ")",
      "and",
      "1912",
      "he",
      "joined",
      "the",
      "social",
      "democratic",
      "party",
      "of",
      "germany",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "had",
      "been",
      "offered",
      "an",
      "athletic",
      "scholarship",
      "by",
      "colorado",
      "college",
      "but",
      "was",
      "drafted",
      "by",
      "the",
      "united",
      "states",
      "marine",
      "corps",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "was",
      "educated",
      "at",
      "eton",
      "college",
      "and",
      "jesus",
      "college",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "she",
      "also",
      "has",
      "a",
      "degree",
      "in",
      "librarianship",
      "from",
      "the",
      "federal",
      "university",
      "of",
      "rio",
      "grande",
      "do",
      "sul",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "meaney",
      "is",
      "a",
      "supporter",
      "of",
      "sinn",
      "féin",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "between",
      "1951",
      "and",
      "1953",
      ",",
      "he",
      "studied",
      "at",
      "cornell",
      "university",
      "and",
      "the",
      "university",
      "of",
      "rochester",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "justin",
      "peelle",
      ",",
      "national",
      "football",
      "league",
      "tight",
      "end",
      "with",
      "the",
      "san",
      "francisco",
      "49ers"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "rollins",
      "a.",
      "emerson",
      "(",
      "professor",
      "1914",
      "–",
      "1942",
      ")",
      "–",
      "member",
      "of",
      "the",
      "national",
      "academy",
      "of",
      "sciences"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "was",
      "managed",
      "by",
      "the",
      "ghostly",
      "character",
      "that",
      "was",
      "paul",
      "bearer",
      "and",
      "tagged",
      "with",
      "his",
      "half",
      "brother",
      "kane",
      "in",
      "brothers",
      "of",
      "destruction",
      "stable",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "maki",
      "'s",
      "look",
      "was",
      "inspired",
      "in",
      "part",
      "by",
      "in",
      "diane",
      "lane",
      "in",
      "the",
      "film",
      "streets",
      "of",
      "fire",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "william",
      "butler",
      "yeats",
      ",",
      "irish",
      "poetry",
      "poet",
      "published",
      "in",
      "the",
      "english",
      "poetry",
      ":"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "jump",
      "'n",
      "bump",
      "is",
      "a",
      "multiplayer",
      "battle",
      "game",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "pinky",
      "wore",
      "the",
      "same",
      "outfit",
      "as",
      "in",
      "her",
      "happy",
      "days",
      "episodes",
      ",",
      "though",
      "her",
      "hair",
      "was",
      "now",
      "in",
      "a",
      "70s",
      "style",
      "shag",
      "cut",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "push",
      "(",
      "country",
      "version",
      ",",
      "from",
      "vh1",
      "storytellers",
      ")",
      "–",
      "3",
      ":",
      "40"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "also",
      "appeared",
      "in",
      "the",
      "movie",
      "silkwood",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "tōru",
      "iwatani",
      ",",
      "game",
      "designer",
      ",",
      "creator",
      "of",
      "pac-man"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "his",
      "last",
      "theatrical",
      "composition",
      "was",
      "music",
      "for",
      "joan",
      "the",
      "woman",
      ",",
      "starring",
      "geraldine",
      "farrar",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "reviews",
      "ron",
      "howard",
      "frost/nixon",
      "and",
      "baz",
      "luhrmann",
      "australia",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "B-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "hustle",
      "(",
      "bbc",
      "one",
      "2004",
      "–",
      "2012",
      ")"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "is",
      "a",
      "romantic",
      "comedy",
      "adventure",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "cover",
      "parodies",
      "that",
      "of",
      "the",
      "guns",
      "n’",
      "roses",
      "album",
      "appetite",
      "for",
      "destruction",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "adapted",
      "from",
      "philip",
      "k.",
      "dick",
      "1977",
      "a",
      "scanner",
      "darkly",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "is",
      "perhaps",
      "best",
      "remembered",
      "for",
      "his",
      "score",
      "for",
      "the",
      "film",
      "laura",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "alternative",
      "name",
      "for",
      "opera",
      "buffa",
      ",",
      "18th",
      "/",
      "early",
      "19th",
      "century",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "2014",
      ",",
      "bryan",
      "adams",
      "recorded",
      "a",
      "version",
      "for",
      "his",
      "album",
      "tracks",
      "of",
      "my",
      "years",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "“",
      "now",
      ",",
      "kasama",
      "rin",
      "ako",
      "sa",
      "bagong",
      "soap",
      "na",
      "‘",
      "healing",
      "hearts",
      "’",
      "with",
      "kristoffer",
      "martin",
      ".",
      "”"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "municipal",
      "seat",
      "is",
      "buenavista",
      "de",
      "cuéllar",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "a",
      "demise",
      "in",
      "the",
      "wake",
      "of",
      "the",
      "creation",
      "of",
      "the",
      "german",
      "empire",
      "under",
      "wilhelm",
      "i",
      "of",
      "germany",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "also",
      "worked",
      "at",
      "the",
      "kyiv",
      "office",
      "of",
      "ernst",
      "&",
      "young",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "lies",
      "approximately",
      "south",
      "east",
      "of",
      "prabuty",
      ",",
      "east",
      "of",
      "kwidzyn",
      ",",
      "and",
      "south",
      "east",
      "of",
      "the",
      "regional",
      "capital",
      "gdańsk",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "is",
      "found",
      "in",
      "people's",
      "republic",
      "of",
      "china",
      ",",
      "indonesia",
      ",",
      "laos",
      ",",
      "malaysia",
      ",",
      "and",
      "vietnam",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "where",
      "is",
      "hofreistæ",
      "located"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "town",
      "does",
      "retain",
      "connections",
      "to",
      "swansea",
      "and",
      "shrewsbury",
      "from",
      "llandrindod",
      "railway",
      "station",
      "on",
      "the",
      "heart",
      "of",
      "wales",
      "line",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "these",
      "early",
      "verses",
      ",",
      "a",
      "literary",
      "style",
      "obviously",
      "influenced",
      "by",
      "petrarch",
      ",",
      "were",
      "finally",
      "published",
      "with",
      "his",
      "agreement",
      "in",
      "1844",
      ",",
      "in",
      "livorno",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "denham",
      ";",
      "it",
      "was",
      "never",
      "connected",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "work",
      "was",
      "about",
      "the",
      "important",
      "for",
      "the",
      "studies",
      "of",
      "the",
      "entire",
      "area",
      "between",
      "the",
      "senegal",
      "river",
      "and",
      "sierra",
      "leone",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "file",
      ":",
      "banana",
      "cue",
      ".",
      "jpg",
      "|",
      "banana",
      "cue",
      ",",
      "a",
      "popular",
      "street",
      "food",
      "from",
      "the",
      "philippines",
      ",",
      "is",
      "made",
      "from",
      "fried",
      "saba",
      "bananas",
      "coated",
      "in",
      "caramelized",
      "sugar"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "after",
      "the",
      "death",
      "of",
      "his",
      "father",
      "in",
      "1957",
      ",",
      "he",
      "spent",
      "his",
      "childhood",
      "with",
      "his",
      "grandmother",
      "in",
      "dresden",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "primatt",
      "was",
      "born",
      "in",
      "london",
      ",",
      "in",
      "1734",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "r",
      ".",
      "grovesi",
      "is",
      "only",
      "known",
      "from",
      "the",
      "island",
      "of",
      "sulawesi",
      "in",
      "indonesia",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "his",
      "father",
      "died",
      "when",
      "he",
      "was",
      "two",
      "and",
      "a",
      "half",
      ",",
      "and",
      "he",
      "grew",
      "up",
      "with",
      "his",
      "mother",
      ",",
      "grandmother",
      "who",
      "was",
      "also",
      "a",
      "portrait",
      "painter",
      ",",
      "and",
      "two",
      "sisters",
      "in",
      "guildford",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "forgotten",
      ",",
      "(",
      ")",
      "is",
      "a",
      "2012",
      "taiwan",
      "television",
      "film",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "is",
      "served",
      "by",
      "koleje",
      "mazowieckie",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "p",
      ".",
      "139b",
      "was",
      "the",
      "result",
      "of",
      "design",
      "work",
      "from",
      "the",
      "former",
      "blackburn",
      "aircraft",
      "design",
      "team",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "jobspice",
      "went",
      "through",
      "the",
      "business",
      "accelerator",
      "y",
      "combinator",
      "in",
      "the",
      "fall",
      "of",
      "2009",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "major",
      "companies",
      "such",
      "as",
      "ibm",
      ",",
      "enel",
      ",",
      "luxottica",
      ",",
      "pricewaterhousecoopers",
      "and",
      "vodafone",
      "continued",
      "to",
      "allow",
      "employees",
      "to",
      "work",
      "from",
      "home",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "canada",
      "'s",
      "kit",
      "are",
      "currently",
      "supplied",
      "by",
      "nike",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "kuwaiti",
      "airlines",
      "jazeera",
      "airways",
      "has",
      "laid",
      "off",
      "320",
      "employees",
      ",",
      "or",
      "roughly",
      "37",
      "%",
      "of",
      "its",
      "workforce",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "music",
      "was",
      "composed",
      "by",
      "aadesh",
      "shrivastava",
      "and",
      "released",
      "by",
      "saregama",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "they",
      "were",
      "soon",
      "placed",
      "under",
      "contract",
      "by",
      "fred",
      "weintraub",
      ",",
      "owner",
      "of",
      "the",
      "bitter",
      "end",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "statistics",
      "of",
      "ligue",
      "2",
      "in",
      "the",
      "1936",
      "–",
      "37",
      "season",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "for",
      "the",
      "enterprise",
      "market",
      ",",
      "gartner",
      "estimates",
      "that",
      "market",
      "penetration",
      "for",
      "field",
      "service",
      "applications",
      "has",
      "reached",
      "25",
      "%",
      "of",
      "the",
      "addressable",
      "market",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "was",
      "the",
      "setting",
      "of",
      "an",
      "episode",
      "of",
      "the",
      "netflix",
      "series",
      "sense8",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "boyd",
      "was",
      "a",
      "timber",
      "merchant",
      "and",
      "sawmill",
      "owner",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "a",
      "special",
      "helpline",
      "was",
      "established",
      "by",
      "the",
      "health",
      "service",
      "executive",
      "in",
      "the",
      "aftermath",
      "of",
      "the",
      "crash",
      ",",
      "while",
      "leaflets",
      "offering",
      "advice",
      "were",
      "distributed",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "1934",
      ",",
      "he",
      "left",
      "farming",
      "to",
      "work",
      "in",
      "the",
      "south",
      "african",
      "broadcasting",
      "corporation",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "partner",
      "benefits",
      "are",
      "more",
      "common",
      "among",
      "large",
      "employers",
      ",",
      "colleges",
      "and",
      "universities",
      "than",
      "at",
      "small",
      "business",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "ten",
      "episode",
      "series",
      "was",
      "produced",
      "for",
      "the",
      "discovery",
      "channel",
      ",",
      "and",
      "first",
      "broadcast",
      "in",
      "2004",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "on",
      "motorcycle",
      ",",
      "a",
      "narrow",
      "rim",
      "will",
      "alter",
      "the",
      "tire",
      "profile",
      ",",
      "concentrating",
      "tire",
      "wear",
      "in",
      "a",
      "very",
      "small",
      "area",
      "during",
      "cornering",
      ",",
      "with",
      "a",
      "smaller",
      "contact",
      "patch",
      "during",
      "braking",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "glyceraldehyde",
      "3",
      "phosphate",
      "occurs",
      "as",
      "a",
      "reactant",
      "in",
      "the",
      "biosynthesis",
      "pathway",
      "of",
      "β-amin",
      "(",
      "vitamin",
      "b1",
      ")",
      ",",
      "another",
      "substance",
      "that",
      "can",
      "not",
      "be",
      "produced",
      "by",
      "the",
      "human",
      "body"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "his",
      "work",
      "on",
      "the",
      "chemistry",
      "of",
      "milk",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "is",
      "also",
      "used",
      "in",
      "cosmetics",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "cessna",
      "citation",
      "longitude",
      "–",
      "in",
      "production",
      "since",
      "2017"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "hotchkiss",
      "m201",
      "(",
      "french",
      "produced",
      "version",
      "of",
      "the",
      "willys",
      "mb",
      ")"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "outerwear",
      "from",
      "the",
      "waist",
      "to",
      "the",
      "ankles",
      "(",
      "trousers",
      ")",
      "*"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "seasons",
      "six",
      ",",
      "seven",
      ",",
      "eight",
      ",",
      "nine",
      "and",
      "ten",
      "have",
      "been",
      "released",
      "for",
      "blu-ray",
      "disc",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "the",
      "nickel",
      "compound",
      "ni",
      "(",
      "c2h4",
      ")",
      "(",
      "pph3",
      ")",
      "2",
      "the",
      "value",
      "is",
      "143",
      "pm",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "final",
      "products",
      "include",
      "bar",
      "stock",
      "and",
      "wire",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "a",
      "gaff",
      "is",
      "a",
      "piece",
      "of",
      "fabric",
      ",",
      "usually",
      "augmented",
      "by",
      "an",
      "elastic",
      "such",
      "as",
      "a",
      "rubber",
      "band",
      ",",
      "that",
      "is",
      "designed",
      "to",
      "hide",
      "the",
      "male",
      "genital",
      "bulge",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "aliero",
      "town",
      "is",
      "surrounded",
      "by",
      "mango",
      "trees",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "version",
      "1.5.1",
      "also",
      "added",
      "support",
      "for",
      "the",
      "new",
      "macbook",
      "pro",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "a",
      "row",
      "of",
      "three",
      "houses",
      "in",
      "stucco",
      "brick",
      "at",
      "the",
      "front",
      "and",
      "stone",
      "elsewhere",
      "with",
      "stone",
      "slate",
      "roofs",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "around",
      "seven",
      "thousand",
      "years",
      "ago",
      ",",
      "the",
      "first",
      "sign",
      "of",
      "copper",
      "jewellery",
      "was",
      "seen",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  }
]