[
  {
    "text": [
      "replaced",
      "don",
      "shula",
      "who",
      "retired",
      "after",
      "the",
      "1995",
      "season",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "harukawa",
      "eizan",
      ",",
      "an",
      "ukiyo-e",
      "artist",
      "active",
      "in",
      "the",
      "1790s"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "adapted",
      "from",
      "philip",
      "k.",
      "dick",
      "1977",
      "a",
      "scanner",
      "darkly",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "la",
      "maison",
      "sous",
      "les",
      "arbres",
      "aka",
      "the",
      "deadly",
      "trap",
      "imdb",
      "director",
      ":",
      "rené",
      "clément"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "during",
      "the",
      "concert",
      "in",
      "san",
      "juan",
      ",",
      "the",
      "vocalist",
      "ross",
      "lynch",
      "record",
      "his",
      "television",
      "film",
      "teen",
      "beach",
      "movie",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "dick",
      "todd",
      "served",
      "as",
      "interim",
      "for",
      "the",
      "rest",
      "of",
      "the",
      "season",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "helen",
      "reddy",
      "recorded",
      "the",
      "song",
      "for",
      "all",
      "this",
      "and",
      "world",
      "war",
      "ii",
      ",",
      "a",
      "1976",
      "film",
      "in",
      "which",
      "wartime",
      "newsreel",
      "was",
      "set",
      "to",
      "a",
      "soundtrack",
      "of",
      "lennon",
      "–",
      "mccartney",
      "songs",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "sold",
      "a",
      "samuel",
      "peploe",
      ",",
      "but",
      "in",
      "particular",
      "he",
      "was",
      "successful",
      "with",
      "his",
      "thomas",
      "moran",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "a&m",
      "records",
      "long",
      "occupied",
      "a",
      "studio",
      "off",
      "sunset",
      "boulevard",
      "built",
      "by",
      "charlie",
      "chaplin",
      "(",
      "who",
      "wrote",
      "the",
      "music",
      "for",
      "his",
      "own",
      "films",
      ")",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "elvin",
      "asked",
      "owen",
      "williams",
      "if",
      "the",
      "stadium",
      "could",
      "be",
      "adapted",
      "for",
      "the",
      "new",
      "sport",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "senators",
      "mark",
      "pryor",
      ",",
      "jerry",
      "moran",
      ",",
      "john",
      "thune",
      ",",
      "tom",
      "udall",
      ",",
      "and",
      "mark",
      "udall",
      "jointly",
      "introduced",
      "the",
      "bill",
      "and",
      "were",
      "all",
      "strong",
      "supporters",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "1884",
      "the",
      "brewery",
      "was",
      "visited",
      "by",
      "j.",
      "c.",
      "jacobsen",
      ",",
      "the",
      "founder",
      "of",
      "carlsberg",
      "group",
      "in",
      "denmark",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "she",
      "added",
      "that",
      "daniel",
      "sousa",
      "has",
      "an",
      "integral",
      "role",
      "to",
      "play",
      "in",
      "the",
      "episode",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "delegation",
      "consisted",
      "of",
      "sprinters",
      "tavevele",
      "noa",
      "and",
      "asenate",
      "manoa",
      "and",
      "weightlifter",
      "tuau",
      "lapua",
      "lapua",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "fognini",
      "'s",
      "run",
      "again",
      "ended",
      "at",
      "the",
      "hands",
      "of",
      "crowd",
      "favourite",
      "andy",
      "roddick",
      "in",
      "a",
      "dramatic",
      "match",
      "(",
      "in",
      "which",
      "he",
      "notably",
      "out",
      "aced",
      "the",
      "american",
      ")",
      "in",
      "four",
      "sets",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "russell",
      "'s",
      "brother",
      "tony",
      "dingwall",
      "is",
      "also",
      "a",
      "professional",
      "footballer",
      "and",
      "they",
      "both",
      "currently",
      "play",
      "alongside",
      "each",
      "other",
      "at",
      "elgin",
      "city",
      "f.c.",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "sweetland",
      "followed",
      "this",
      "up",
      "by",
      "stepping",
      "into",
      "the",
      "supervising",
      "animator",
      "role",
      "on",
      "john",
      "lasseter",
      "cars",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "B-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "donna",
      "summer",
      "opened",
      "the",
      "show",
      "with",
      "she",
      "works",
      "hard",
      "for",
      "the",
      "money",
      ",",
      "and",
      "a",
      "tribute",
      "to",
      "working",
      "women",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "his",
      "compositions",
      "display",
      "the",
      "influence",
      "of",
      "utagawa",
      "hiroshige",
      "in",
      "how",
      "objects",
      "in",
      "the",
      "frame",
      "are",
      "often",
      "cut",
      "off",
      "at",
      "the",
      "edges",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "fireball",
      "roberts",
      "would",
      "qualify",
      "for",
      "the",
      "pole",
      "position",
      "at",
      "the",
      "speed",
      "of",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "anthony",
      "recker",
      ",",
      "former",
      "professional",
      "baseball",
      "player",
      ",",
      "atlanta",
      "braves",
      ",",
      "chicago",
      "cubs",
      ",",
      "new",
      "york",
      "mets",
      "and",
      "oakland",
      "athletics"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "beat",
      "structure",
      "has",
      "also",
      "been",
      "compared",
      "to",
      "britney",
      "spears",
      "’",
      "2011",
      "single",
      ",",
      "hold",
      "it",
      "against",
      "me",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "richard",
      "titmuss",
      ",",
      "founder",
      "of",
      "the",
      "academic",
      "discipline",
      "of",
      "social",
      "policy"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "forces",
      "under",
      "niketa",
      "thopia",
      "are",
      "heavily",
      "defeated",
      "during",
      "a",
      "skirmish",
      "with",
      "forces",
      "under",
      "theodor",
      "corona",
      "musachi",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "john",
      "weider",
      "—",
      "guitar",
      ",",
      "violin",
      ",",
      "backing",
      "vocals"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "who",
      "is",
      "cecil",
      "pugh"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "watkins",
      "has",
      "an",
      "ongoing",
      "feud",
      "with",
      "bill",
      "o'reilly",
      "from",
      "fox",
      "news",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "ice",
      "is",
      "a",
      "novel",
      "by",
      "anna",
      "kavan",
      ",",
      "published",
      "in",
      "1967",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "lick",
      "it",
      "up",
      "(",
      "vinnie",
      "vincent",
      ",",
      "stanley",
      ")",
      "–",
      "3",
      ":",
      "16"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "victor",
      "svendsen",
      "11",
      "–",
      "7",
      ",",
      "11",
      "–",
      "7",
      ",",
      "8",
      "–",
      "11",
      ",",
      "10",
      "–",
      "12",
      ",",
      "11",
      "–",
      "4"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "from",
      "1947",
      ",",
      "she",
      "studied",
      "at",
      "the",
      "royal",
      "danish",
      "academy",
      "of",
      "fine",
      "arts",
      "under",
      "vilhelm",
      "lundstrøm",
      ",",
      "kræsten",
      "iversen",
      "and",
      "elof",
      "risebye",
      ",",
      "graduating",
      "in",
      "1955",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "if",
      "you",
      "had",
      "my",
      "love",
      "(",
      "rodney",
      "jerkins",
      "radio",
      "edit",
      ")",
      "—",
      "4",
      ":",
      "00"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "also",
      "collaborated",
      "on",
      "songs",
      "with",
      "disclosure",
      "and",
      "gallant",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "however",
      "she",
      "has",
      "to",
      "settle",
      "for",
      "silver",
      "medal",
      "after",
      "she",
      "lost",
      "to",
      "akane",
      "yamaguchi",
      "in",
      "a",
      "tightly",
      "contested",
      "final",
      "match",
      "of",
      "3",
      "games",
      "21",
      "–",
      "14",
      ",",
      "18",
      "–",
      "21",
      ",",
      "13",
      "–",
      "21",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "gene",
      "kelly",
      "had",
      "a",
      "special",
      "affection",
      "for",
      "her",
      "and",
      "included",
      "her",
      "in",
      "each",
      "of",
      "his",
      "films",
      "following",
      "her",
      "role",
      "in",
      "an",
      "american",
      "in",
      "paris",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "philosopher",
      "and",
      "historian",
      ",",
      "władysław",
      "tatarkiewicz",
      ",",
      "was",
      "his",
      "grandson",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "combination",
      "of",
      "televoting",
      "(",
      "50",
      "%",
      ")",
      "and",
      "the",
      "votes",
      "of",
      "an",
      "expert",
      "jury",
      "(",
      "50",
      "%",
      ")",
      "selected",
      "time",
      "to",
      "shine",
      "performed",
      "by",
      "mélanie",
      "rené",
      "as",
      "the",
      "winner",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "like",
      "him",
      "some",
      "other",
      "celebrities",
      "did",
      "the",
      "same",
      "for",
      "example",
      "felix",
      "baumgartner",
      "(",
      "in",
      "bucharest",
      ")",
      "and",
      "david",
      "coulthard",
      "(",
      "in",
      "silverstone",
      ")",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "my",
      "foolish",
      "heart",
      "(",
      "victor",
      "young",
      ",",
      "ned",
      "washington",
      ")",
      "–",
      "6",
      ":",
      "34"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "early",
      "in",
      "the",
      "series",
      ",",
      "actress",
      "jasika",
      "nicole",
      "feared",
      "her",
      "character",
      "was",
      "going",
      "to",
      "become",
      "liked",
      "by",
      "the",
      "audience",
      "only",
      "to",
      "suddenly",
      "die",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "a",
      "notable",
      "exception",
      "from",
      "graveyards",
      "are",
      "the",
      "juru",
      "kunci",
      "who",
      "maintain",
      "a",
      "presence",
      "on",
      "the",
      "side",
      "of",
      "volcanoes",
      "such",
      "as",
      "mbah",
      "maridjan",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "the",
      "semifinal",
      ",",
      "they",
      "lost",
      "to",
      "the",
      "tracy",
      "fleury",
      "rink",
      "9",
      "–",
      "4",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "first",
      "did",
      "so",
      "in",
      "1992",
      "alongside",
      "mark",
      "pinger",
      ",",
      "dirk",
      "richter",
      ",",
      "and",
      "steffen",
      "zesner",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "then",
      "signed",
      "for",
      "k.v.c.",
      "westerlo",
      "where",
      "he",
      "was",
      "supposed",
      "to",
      "replace",
      "chris",
      "janssens",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "chadli",
      "amri",
      "–",
      "1.",
      "fsv",
      "mainz",
      "05",
      ",",
      "1.",
      "fc",
      "kaiserslautern",
      "–",
      "2006",
      "–",
      "07",
      ",",
      "2009",
      "–",
      "11"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "heroes",
      "and",
      "villains",
      "(",
      "alternate",
      "take",
      ")",
      "–",
      "the",
      "beach",
      "boys"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "harper",
      "enrolled",
      "at",
      "the",
      "university",
      "of",
      "toronto",
      "but",
      "dropped",
      "out",
      "after",
      "two",
      "months",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "brian",
      "fallon",
      "(",
      "born",
      "1980",
      ")",
      ",",
      "guitarist",
      "and",
      "lead",
      "vocalist",
      "for",
      "the",
      "gaslight",
      "anthem",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "his",
      "nephew",
      "is",
      "communist",
      "party",
      "of",
      "india",
      "(marxist)",
      "politburo",
      "member",
      ",",
      "sitaram",
      "yechury",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "1963",
      ",",
      "like",
      "in",
      "1974",
      ",",
      "the",
      "rumor",
      "was",
      "that",
      "the",
      "german",
      "football",
      "association",
      "chairman",
      "hermann",
      "neuberger",
      ",",
      "a",
      "native",
      "of",
      "the",
      "saarland",
      "and",
      "honorary",
      "member",
      "of",
      "the",
      "1",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "her",
      "analysis",
      "of",
      "this",
      "play",
      "formed",
      "the",
      "basis",
      "of",
      "her",
      "ph",
      ".",
      "d",
      ".",
      "thesis",
      ",",
      "in",
      "1933",
      ",",
      "from",
      "johns",
      "hopkins",
      "university",
      ",",
      "under",
      "the",
      "supervision",
      "of",
      "henry",
      "carrington",
      "lancaster",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "airport",
      "is",
      "also",
      "home",
      "to",
      "one",
      "of",
      "the",
      "three",
      "wales",
      "air",
      "ambulance",
      "helicopters",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "klinghoffer",
      "was",
      "said",
      "to",
      "have",
      "recorded",
      "on",
      "at",
      "least",
      "one",
      "track",
      "on",
      "former",
      "jane's",
      "addiction",
      "bassist",
      "eric",
      "avery",
      "second",
      "solo",
      "album",
      ",",
      "however",
      "life",
      ".",
      "time",
      ".",
      "did",
      "not",
      "include",
      "it",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "was",
      "even",
      "featured",
      "in",
      "the",
      "irish",
      "independent",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "is",
      "a",
      "supporter",
      "of",
      "rangers",
      "f.c.",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "she",
      "later",
      "received",
      "formal",
      "training",
      "at",
      "the",
      "american",
      "academy",
      "of",
      "dramatic",
      "arts",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "røyken",
      "videregående",
      "skole",
      "is",
      "an",
      "unesco",
      "aspnet",
      "school",
      ",",
      "and",
      "offers",
      "several",
      "international",
      "exchange",
      "programs",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "get",
      "your",
      "gunn",
      "(",
      "marilyn",
      "manson",
      ")",
      "–",
      "3",
      ":",
      "19"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "is",
      "one",
      "of",
      "five",
      "gardens",
      "of",
      "the",
      "non",
      "profit",
      "national",
      "tropical",
      "botanical",
      "garden",
      "(",
      "ntbg",
      ")",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "then",
      "joined",
      "the",
      "jatiya",
      "party",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "moselle",
      "'s",
      "6th",
      "constituency",
      ":",
      "cartography",
      ",",
      "french",
      "national",
      "assembly"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "to",
      "east",
      "african",
      "railways",
      "and",
      "harbours",
      "corporation",
      "1006",
      "–",
      "1008",
      ";",
      "ear&h",
      "class",
      "10"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "graduated",
      "from",
      "the",
      "illinois",
      "state",
      "university",
      "at",
      "normal",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "associated",
      "press",
      "described",
      "it",
      "as",
      "cocky",
      "but",
      "alluring",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "she",
      "recorded",
      "a",
      "remake",
      "of",
      "strawberry",
      "fields",
      "forever",
      "by",
      "the",
      "beatles",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "painting",
      "itself",
      "is",
      "at",
      "mount",
      "stewart",
      ",",
      "newtownards",
      ",",
      "northern",
      "ireland",
      ",",
      "and",
      "is",
      "the",
      "property",
      "of",
      "the",
      "national",
      "trust",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "to",
      "farciot",
      "edouart",
      "and",
      "the",
      "paramount",
      "pictures",
      "for",
      "an",
      "automatic",
      "electric",
      "transparency",
      "cueing",
      "timer",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "his",
      "second",
      "game",
      ",",
      "against",
      "the",
      "brisbane",
      "broncos",
      ",",
      "he",
      "scored",
      "a",
      "try",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "db",
      "class",
      "66",
      "was",
      "planned",
      "by",
      "the",
      "deutsche",
      "bundesbahn",
      "for",
      "fast",
      "freight",
      "and",
      "passenger",
      "train",
      "services",
      "on",
      "main",
      "and",
      "branch",
      "lines",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "stoddart",
      "joined",
      "the",
      "labour",
      "party",
      "in",
      "1947",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "she",
      "produced",
      "and",
      "presented",
      "for",
      "the",
      "bbc",
      "radio",
      "3",
      "before",
      "leading",
      "the",
      "development",
      "of",
      "new",
      "work",
      "for",
      "english",
      "national",
      "opera",
      "between",
      "1998",
      "and",
      "2001",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "also",
      "turned",
      "to",
      "producing",
      ",",
      "hitting",
      "the",
      "studio",
      "with",
      "motion",
      "city",
      "soundtrack",
      "to",
      "record",
      "commit",
      "this",
      "to",
      "memory",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "laki",
      "was",
      "awarded",
      "an",
      "honorary",
      "medical",
      "degree",
      "from",
      "the",
      "university",
      "of",
      "debrecen",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "sermanni",
      "finished",
      "his",
      "first",
      "year",
      "as",
      "manager",
      "of",
      "united",
      "states",
      "women's",
      "national",
      "soccer",
      "team",
      "unbeaten",
      "with",
      "13",
      "wins",
      "and",
      "3",
      "draws",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "film",
      "is",
      "available",
      "for",
      "free",
      "at",
      "the",
      "website",
      "of",
      "the",
      "national",
      "library",
      "of",
      "norway",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "farewell",
      "is",
      "the",
      "eighth",
      "studio",
      "recording",
      "released",
      "by",
      "the",
      "toshiko",
      "akiyoshi",
      "–",
      "lew",
      "tabackin",
      "big",
      "band",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "2013",
      ",",
      "the",
      "world",
      "economic",
      "forum",
      "evaluated",
      "countries",
      "in",
      "terms",
      "of",
      "how",
      "successful",
      "they",
      "were",
      "in",
      "advertising",
      "campaigns",
      "to",
      "attract",
      "foreign",
      "visitors",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "his",
      "first",
      "job",
      "was",
      "as",
      "a",
      "travel",
      "secretary",
      "for",
      "the",
      "norwegian",
      "christian",
      "student",
      "and",
      "school",
      "association",
      "from",
      "1948",
      "1953",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "for",
      "instance",
      ",",
      "the",
      "story",
      "the",
      "dying",
      "night",
      "appears",
      "to",
      "contradict",
      "the",
      "background",
      "of",
      "the",
      "singing",
      "bell",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "designed",
      "the",
      "xerox",
      "alto",
      ",",
      "which",
      "is",
      "the",
      "first",
      "computer",
      "that",
      "used",
      "a",
      "mouse",
      "driven",
      "graphical",
      "user",
      "interface",
      "(",
      "gui",
      ")",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "various",
      "androids",
      "called",
      "hosts",
      "in",
      "the",
      "hbo",
      "series",
      "westworld",
      "(",
      "2016",
      "–",
      ")",
      ",",
      "based",
      "on",
      "the",
      "westworld"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "films",
      "featured",
      "former",
      "footballer",
      "and",
      "commentator",
      "robbie",
      "savage",
      "and",
      "countdown",
      "co",
      "host",
      "rachel",
      "riley",
      "among",
      "others",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "you've",
      "changed",
      "(",
      "bill",
      "carey",
      ",",
      "carl",
      "t.",
      "fischer",
      ")",
      "4",
      ":",
      "09"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "webb",
      "received",
      "critical",
      "acclaim",
      "for",
      "his",
      "screenplays",
      "for",
      "cape",
      "fear",
      "and",
      "how",
      "the",
      "west",
      "was",
      "won",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "dvd",
      "the",
      "life",
      "of",
      "emile",
      "zola",
      "(",
      "aap",
      "print",
      ")"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "roary",
      "the",
      "racing",
      "car",
      ",",
      "an",
      "animated",
      "children",
      "'s",
      "television",
      "show",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "was",
      "one",
      "of",
      "the",
      "translators",
      "of",
      "the",
      "new",
      "living",
      "translation",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "a",
      "third",
      "game",
      ",",
      "titled",
      "bye-bye",
      "boxboy!",
      ",",
      "was",
      "released",
      "in",
      "2017",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "her",
      "debut",
      "album",
      "was",
      "named",
      "eye",
      "to",
      "the",
      "telescope",
      "the",
      "name",
      "was",
      "inspired",
      "by",
      "her",
      "childhood",
      "experiences",
      "at",
      "her",
      "father",
      "'s",
      "physics",
      "laboratory",
      "at",
      "university",
      "of",
      "st",
      "andrews",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "most",
      "of",
      "the",
      "movies",
      "produced",
      "nowadays",
      "are",
      "comedy",
      "film",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "story",
      "had",
      "also",
      "been",
      "made",
      "into",
      "a",
      "the",
      "happy",
      "time",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "was",
      "their",
      "first",
      "single",
      "from",
      "their",
      "debut",
      "extended",
      "play",
      "black",
      "smoke",
      "rising",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "pianist",
      "–",
      "ronald",
      "harwood",
      "based",
      "on",
      "the",
      "pianist",
      "by",
      "władysław",
      "szpilman"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "capcom",
      "purchased",
      "the",
      "intellectual",
      "property",
      "in",
      "2012",
      "and",
      "provided",
      "funding",
      "for",
      "the",
      "project",
      ",",
      "reimagining",
      "it",
      "as",
      "an",
      "action-adventure",
      "game",
      "for",
      "release",
      "on",
      "multiple",
      "platforms",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "bee",
      "movie",
      "(",
      "visual",
      "development",
      "artist",
      ")"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "what",
      "are",
      "are",
      "you",
      "happy?"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "april",
      "fools",
      "(",
      "burt",
      "bacharach",
      ",",
      "hal",
      "david",
      ")",
      "–",
      "3",
      ":",
      "43"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "takkar",
      ",",
      "english",
      "babu",
      "desi",
      "mem",
      ",",
      "zakham",
      ",",
      "sarfarosh",
      ",",
      "hamara",
      "dil",
      "aapke",
      "paas",
      "hai"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "is",
      "available",
      "for",
      "purchase",
      "in",
      "the",
      "itunes",
      "store",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "winner",
      ":",
      "pop",
      "idol",
      "(",
      "thames",
      "television",
      "/",
      "19",
      "entertainment",
      "/",
      "itv",
      ")"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "second",
      "arc",
      "of",
      "the",
      "comic",
      "book",
      "paper",
      "girls",
      "features",
      "a",
      "pair",
      "of",
      "tardigrades",
      "that",
      "have",
      "been",
      "enlarged",
      "to",
      "a",
      "massive",
      "size",
      "as",
      "a",
      "side",
      "effect",
      "of",
      "time",
      "travel",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "l.a.",
      "confidential",
      "–",
      "curtis",
      "hanson",
      "and",
      "brian",
      "helgeland"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "brooks",
      "next",
      "project",
      "came",
      "in",
      "1983",
      ",",
      "when",
      "he",
      "wrote",
      ",",
      "produced",
      "and",
      "directed",
      "terms",
      "of",
      "endearment",
      ",",
      "adapting",
      "the",
      "screenplay",
      "from",
      "larry",
      "mcmurtry",
      "novel",
      "of",
      "the",
      "same",
      "name",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "humppa",
      "!",
      "is",
      "a",
      "2001",
      "compilation",
      "album",
      "by",
      "eläkeläiset",
      ",",
      "mainly",
      "released",
      "to",
      "the",
      "russia",
      "market",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "need",
      "for",
      "speed:",
      "prostreet",
      ",",
      "burnout",
      "3:",
      "takedown",
      ",",
      "and",
      "burnout",
      "dominator",
      "use",
      "autobahn",
      "as",
      "one",
      "of",
      "their",
      "tracks",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "september",
      "26",
      "–",
      "linda",
      "hamilton",
      ",",
      "actress",
      "(",
      "the",
      "terminator",
      ")"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "presenting",
      "the",
      "nos",
      "journaal",
      "from",
      "1996",
      "till",
      "2009",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "foreign",
      "policy",
      "magazine",
      ",",
      "he",
      "describes",
      "how",
      "the",
      "new",
      "geopolitics",
      "of",
      "food",
      "has",
      ",",
      "in",
      "2011",
      ",",
      "already",
      "begun",
      "to",
      "contribute",
      "to",
      "revolutions",
      "and",
      "upheaval",
      "in",
      "various",
      "countries",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "a",
      "port",
      "for",
      "ms-dos",
      "also",
      "exists",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "added",
      "that",
      "it",
      "sounds",
      "like",
      "a",
      "who",
      "’s",
      "who",
      "of",
      "spotify",
      "buzz",
      "bands",
      ",",
      "a",
      "time",
      "stamped",
      "memo",
      "alerting",
      "music",
      "executives",
      "to",
      "the",
      "mainstream",
      "’s",
      "idea",
      "of",
      "indie",
      "rock",
      "[",
      ".",
      ".",
      ".",
      "]"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "film",
      "is",
      "loosely",
      "based",
      "on",
      "the",
      "play",
      "the",
      "moods",
      "of",
      "marianne",
      "by",
      "alfred",
      "de",
      "musset",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "giuseppe",
      "verdi",
      ":",
      "aida",
      "(",
      "1993",
      ",",
      "2013",
      ")"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "x-play",
      "gave",
      "the",
      "game",
      "a",
      "5",
      "out",
      "of",
      "5",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "this",
      "marine",
      "species",
      "occurs",
      "off",
      "hong",
      "kong",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "haßloch",
      ",",
      "along",
      "with",
      "the",
      "neighbouring",
      "municipality",
      "of",
      "böhl-iggelheim",
      ",",
      "is",
      "also",
      "home",
      "to",
      "one",
      "of",
      "the",
      "28",
      "“",
      "public-access",
      "television",
      "”",
      "in",
      "rhineland-palatinate",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "mogzon",
      "is",
      "a",
      "railway",
      "station",
      "of",
      "the",
      "trans-siberian",
      "railway",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "gordon",
      "led",
      "his",
      "men",
      "to",
      "a",
      "similar",
      "victory",
      "at",
      "helena",
      "two",
      "weeks",
      "later",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "logo",
      "of",
      "the",
      "program",
      "is",
      "a",
      "distinctive",
      "pyramid",
      "with",
      "a",
      "zoom",
      "like",
      "sound",
      "effect",
      "(",
      "immortalized",
      "as",
      "the",
      "ka",
      "chung",
      ")",
      "for",
      "a",
      "theme",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "a",
      "new",
      "ski",
      "area",
      "west",
      "of",
      "calgary",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "county",
      "donegal",
      "the",
      "first",
      "snows",
      "of",
      "the",
      "season",
      "fell",
      ",",
      "leaving",
      "hundreds",
      "of",
      "residents",
      "without",
      "electricity",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "she",
      "was",
      "born",
      "in",
      "lancaster",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "temporary",
      "and",
      "permanent",
      "premises",
      "are",
      "both",
      "in",
      "geylang",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "country",
      "with",
      "the",
      "largest",
      "number",
      "of",
      "czechs",
      "living",
      "abroad",
      "is",
      "the",
      "united",
      "states",
      "of",
      "america",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "our",
      "conspiracies",
      "are",
      "not",
      "extraordinary",
      ",",
      "but",
      "only",
      "further",
      "evidence",
      "that",
      "our",
      "country",
      "is",
      "subject",
      "to",
      "the",
      "same",
      "laws",
      "of",
      "socialistic",
      "development",
      "as",
      "the",
      "soviet",
      "union",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "a",
      "recent",
      "expansion",
      "to",
      "the",
      "water",
      "treatment",
      "plant",
      "northwest",
      "of",
      "town",
      "will",
      "start",
      "supplying",
      "culinary",
      "water",
      "to",
      "the",
      "community",
      "of",
      "roosevelt",
      "some",
      "away",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "she",
      "was",
      "brought",
      "up",
      "in",
      "chennai",
      ",",
      "moving",
      "to",
      "kochi",
      "after",
      "a",
      "few",
      "years",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "tanaghai",
      "is",
      "a",
      "village",
      "in",
      "guadalcanal",
      ",",
      "solomon",
      "islands",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "was",
      "a",
      "switzerland",
      "hispano-suiza",
      "design",
      ",",
      "with",
      "a",
      "rolls-royce",
      "engine",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "is",
      "endemic",
      "to",
      "sri",
      "lanka",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "is",
      "one",
      "of",
      "eight",
      "constituencies",
      "in",
      "kitui",
      "county",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "was",
      "declared",
      "an",
      "enemy",
      "by",
      "the",
      "yugoslav",
      "partisans",
      ",",
      "and",
      "his",
      "holdings",
      "were",
      "subsequently",
      "confiscated",
      "by",
      "the",
      "socialist",
      "federal",
      "republic",
      "of",
      "yugoslavia",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "attended",
      "the",
      "manchester",
      "grammar",
      "school",
      ",",
      "receiving",
      "a",
      "scholarship",
      "to",
      "balliol",
      "college",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "route",
      "linking",
      "lake",
      "saint-louis",
      "to",
      "the",
      "rivière",
      "des",
      "prairies",
      "dates",
      "back",
      "to",
      "the",
      "early",
      "1700s",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "quickly",
      "became",
      "the",
      "second",
      "city",
      "of",
      "the",
      "kingdom",
      "of",
      "naples",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "bankura",
      "–",
      "masagram",
      "line",
      "is",
      "a",
      "broad",
      "gauge",
      "rail",
      "line",
      "connecting",
      "bankura",
      "and",
      "masagram",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "originally",
      "from",
      "chapel",
      "hill",
      ",",
      "she",
      "graduated",
      "from",
      "harvard",
      "university",
      "in",
      "2004",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "was",
      "buried",
      "underneath",
      "lee",
      "chapel",
      "at",
      "washington",
      "and",
      "lee",
      "university",
      ",",
      "where",
      "his",
      "body",
      "remains",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "is",
      "found",
      "in",
      "costa",
      "rica",
      "and",
      "panama",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "a",
      "1989",
      "poll",
      "ranked",
      "it",
      "as",
      "the",
      "seventh",
      "most",
      "popular",
      "german",
      "democratic",
      "republic",
      "science",
      "fiction",
      "novel",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "after",
      "the",
      "death",
      "of",
      "his",
      "wife",
      "in",
      "1855",
      ",",
      "he",
      "is",
      "believed",
      "to",
      "have",
      "lived",
      "with",
      "a",
      "daughter",
      "at",
      "beloeil",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "to",
      "the",
      "southeast",
      "near",
      "the",
      "city",
      "of",
      "cholula",
      "is",
      "the",
      "great",
      "pyramid",
      "of",
      "cholula",
      ",",
      "visible",
      "from",
      "the",
      "city",
      "center",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "died",
      "in",
      "1988",
      "in",
      "bazancourt",
      ",",
      "near",
      "paris",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "belshina",
      "is",
      "a",
      "tire",
      "manufacturer",
      "in",
      "belarus",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "greater",
      "anglia",
      "operate",
      "hourly",
      "services",
      "to",
      "cambridge",
      "railway",
      "station",
      "and",
      "to",
      "ipswich",
      "railway",
      "station",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "lived",
      "in",
      "barcelona",
      "where",
      "he",
      "frequented",
      "salafi",
      "circles",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "from",
      "1962",
      "to",
      "1965",
      "he",
      "was",
      "ambassador",
      "in",
      "bonn",
      "(",
      "germany",
      ")"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "queen",
      "was",
      "descended",
      "from",
      "the",
      "pagan",
      "kingdom",
      "and",
      "myinsaing",
      "kingdom",
      "royal",
      "lines",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "was",
      "based",
      "in",
      "punjab",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "1837",
      ",",
      "the",
      "yuen",
      "long",
      "bazaar",
      "had",
      "its",
      "market",
      "days",
      "on",
      "the",
      "third",
      ",",
      "sixth",
      ",",
      "and",
      "ninth",
      "days",
      "of",
      "each",
      "month",
      "of",
      "the",
      "lunar",
      "calendar",
      "discounts",
      "on",
      "those",
      "days",
      "were",
      "common",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "B-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "nagano",
      ":",
      "a",
      "core",
      "city",
      ",",
      "the",
      "capital",
      "of",
      "nagano",
      "prefecture"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "1924",
      "–",
      "33",
      ",",
      "he",
      "studied",
      "sculpture",
      "in",
      "vienna",
      ",",
      "berlin",
      "and",
      "paris",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "sebastiano",
      "del",
      "piombo",
      ",",
      "the",
      "raising",
      "of",
      "lazarus",
      ",",
      "and",
      "the",
      "altarpiece",
      "for",
      "chigi",
      "chapel"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "is",
      "also",
      "present",
      "in",
      "the",
      "wild",
      "in",
      "new",
      "zealand",
      ",",
      "where",
      "it",
      "is",
      "of",
      "exotic",
      "origin",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "elections",
      "for",
      "the",
      "water",
      "board",
      "in",
      "the",
      "netherlands",
      "have",
      "some",
      "similarities",
      "to",
      "other",
      "elections",
      "mentioned",
      "above",
      ",",
      "but",
      "also",
      "some",
      "distinctive",
      "differences",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "show",
      "was",
      "aired",
      "live",
      "television",
      "through",
      "cnn",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "there",
      "is",
      "a",
      "growing",
      "interest",
      "in",
      "family",
      "history",
      "in",
      "the",
      "media",
      "as",
      "a",
      "result",
      "of",
      "advertising",
      "and",
      "television",
      "shows",
      "sponsored",
      "by",
      "large",
      "genealogy",
      "companies",
      ",",
      "such",
      "as",
      "ancestry.com",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "jerry",
      "lee",
      "lewis",
      "also",
      "recorded",
      "this",
      "song",
      "in",
      "1963",
      ",",
      "his",
      "final",
      "offer",
      "at",
      "sun",
      "records",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "patrick",
      "e.",
      "haggerty",
      "(",
      "1914",
      "–",
      "1980",
      ")",
      "–",
      "engineer",
      "and",
      "businessman",
      ";",
      "co",
      "founder",
      ",",
      "texas",
      "instruments",
      ";",
      "born",
      "in",
      "harvey"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "berry",
      "was",
      "the",
      "nephew",
      "of",
      "major",
      "league",
      "baseball",
      "pitcher",
      "joe",
      "berry",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "bbc",
      "filmed",
      "a",
      "subsequent",
      "performance",
      "with",
      "its",
      "own",
      "stephen",
      "fry",
      "and",
      "used",
      "footage",
      "in",
      "a",
      "documentary",
      "series",
      "about",
      "language",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
