[
  {
    "text": [
      "his",
      "thriller",
      "strangers",
      "on",
      "a",
      "train",
      "was",
      "based",
      "on",
      "the",
      "strangers",
      "on",
      "a",
      "train",
      "by",
      "patricia",
      "highsmith",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "title",
      "is",
      "a",
      "play",
      "on",
      "words",
      "of",
      "the",
      "1950",
      "nevil",
      "shute",
      "novel",
      "a",
      "town",
      "like",
      "alice",
      ",",
      "although",
      "paul",
      "weller",
      "says",
      "he",
      "had",
      "not",
      "read",
      "the",
      "book",
      "at",
      "the",
      "time",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "venom",
      "appears",
      "in",
      "the",
      "animated",
      "special",
      "lego",
      "marvel",
      "super",
      "heroes:",
      "maximum",
      "overload",
      ",",
      "voiced",
      "by",
      "dee",
      "bradley",
      "baker",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "alain",
      "jessua",
      "for",
      "the",
      "killing",
      "game",
      "(",
      "jeu",
      "de",
      "massacre",
      ")"
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "music",
      "was",
      "composed",
      "by",
      "r.",
      "k.",
      "shekhar",
      "and",
      "the",
      "lyrics",
      "were",
      "written",
      "by",
      "sreekumaran",
      "thampi",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "played",
      "for",
      "the",
      "houston",
      "astros",
      "of",
      "major",
      "league",
      "baseball",
      "(",
      "mlb",
      ")",
      "from",
      "2001",
      "to",
      "2002",
      "and",
      "2004",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "a",
      "review",
      "of",
      "the",
      "study",
      "was",
      "initiated",
      "by",
      "the",
      "university",
      "of",
      "vienna",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "three",
      "are",
      "with",
      "rachel",
      ":",
      "queen",
      "somebody",
      "to",
      "love",
      ",",
      "no",
      "air",
      "and",
      "keep",
      "holding",
      "on",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "he",
      "is",
      "also",
      "currently",
      "a",
      "member",
      "of",
      "iron",
      "butterfly",
      ",",
      "having",
      "previously",
      "performed",
      "with",
      "them",
      "as",
      "a",
      "substitute",
      "for",
      "the",
      "late",
      "lee",
      "dorman",
      "during",
      "the",
      "band",
      "'s",
      "2006",
      "tour",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "logo",
      "of",
      "the",
      "program",
      "is",
      "a",
      "distinctive",
      "pyramid",
      "with",
      "a",
      "zoom",
      "like",
      "sound",
      "effect",
      "(",
      "immortalized",
      "as",
      "the",
      "ka",
      "chung",
      ")",
      "for",
      "a",
      "theme",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "restricted",
      "the",
      "reading",
      "of",
      "the",
      "bible",
      "to",
      "clerics",
      ",",
      "noblemen",
      ",",
      "the",
      "gentry",
      "and",
      "richer",
      "merchants",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "there",
      "is",
      "mention",
      "of",
      "this",
      "koothu",
      "in",
      "silappatikaram",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "motion",
      "city",
      "soundtrack",
      "covered",
      "the",
      "song",
      "on",
      "the",
      "punk",
      "goes",
      "80's",
      "compilation",
      "album",
      ",",
      "released",
      "on",
      "fearless",
      "records",
      "in",
      "2005",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "I-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "then",
      "it",
      "turns",
      "right",
      "flowing",
      "through",
      "the",
      "mountains",
      "and",
      "joins",
      "the",
      "yarkand",
      "river",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "it",
      "is",
      "also",
      "a",
      "dead-end",
      "station",
      "for",
      "the",
      "90.7",
      "kilometer",
      "yonesaka",
      "line",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "the",
      "southern",
      "boundary",
      "was",
      "the",
      "wairau",
      "river",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "freundschaft",
      "siegt",
      "is",
      "an",
      "german",
      "democratic",
      "republic",
      "film",
      "about",
      "the",
      "3rd",
      "world",
      "festival",
      "of",
      "youth",
      "and",
      "students",
      "held",
      "in",
      "berlin",
      "in",
      "1951",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "I-LOC",
      "B-CW",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "libres",
      "y",
      "locos",
      ",",
      "el",
      "gran",
      "silencio",
      ",",
      "1998"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "in",
      "1999",
      ",",
      "he",
      "was",
      "signed",
      "by",
      "laliga",
      "side",
      "valencia",
      "cf",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "O",
      "B-GRP",
      "I-GRP",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "she",
      "was",
      "built",
      "by",
      "the",
      "russian",
      "steam",
      "navigation",
      "and",
      "trading",
      "company",
      "at",
      "sevastopol",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "I-CORP",
      "O",
      "B-LOC",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "their",
      "dkw",
      "rt",
      "125",
      "was",
      "one",
      "of",
      "the",
      "first",
      "motor",
      "vehicles",
      "to",
      "achieve",
      "over",
      "100",
      "mpg",
      "as",
      "a",
      "result",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "functioning",
      "pencil",
      "sharpener",
      "(",
      "leadhead",
      ")",
      "which",
      "transforms",
      "into",
      "techno",
      "jet",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "I-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "men",
      "must",
      "not",
      "shave",
      "their",
      "beards",
      "with",
      "a",
      "razor",
      "—"
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "text": [
      "finally",
      ",",
      "it",
      "is",
      "also",
      "synced",
      "to",
      "an",
      "iphone",
      "app",
      "which",
      "allows",
      "for",
      "tracking",
      "and",
      "sharing",
      "of",
      "personal",
      "record",
      "and",
      "achievements",
      "."
    ],
    "label": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PROD",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  }
]