[
{"text": ["Molay", ",", "Haute-Saône"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Somogy", "County", "(", "former", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Mõisaküla", ",", "Jõgeva", "County"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Kingman", "Reef", "(", "US", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["It", "is", "found", "in", "Mexico", ",", "Guatemala", ",", "Costa", "Rica", ",", "Panama", ",", "Colombia", ",", "Venezuela", "and", "Brazil", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "Pseudosabicea", "''", "N.Hallé", "=", "Sabicea", "''", "Aubl", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Danvers", ",", "Illinois"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Nicaragua", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Wemindji", ",", "Quebec"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Eucharis", "×", "grandiflora"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Bryan", "County", ",", "Oklahoma"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["''", "Ormetica", "sicilia", "''", "(", "Druce", ",", "1884", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Ronald", "Dregan", ":", "Dreganomics"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Jeże", ",", "Warmian-Masurian", "Voivodeship"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["She", "currently", "lives", "in", "Los", "Angeles", ",", "California", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["San", "Cristóbal", "de", "La", "Laguna"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["''", "Bicyclus", "milyas", "''", "(", "Hewitson", ",", "1864", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["/", "255", "or", "256", "Samarra", ",", "Iraq"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC"]},
{"text": ["''", "Calisto", "pulchella", "pulchella", "''", "Lathy", ",", "1899"], "label": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "United", "Provinces", "''", "'", "–"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["East", "Brunswick", ",", "New", "Jersey", "."], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["It", "was", "named", "after", "the", "Darwin", "suburb", "of", "Stuart", "Park", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Erosida", "yucatana", "''", "Giesbert", ",", "1985"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "Crobylophora", "xanthochyta", "''", "Meyrick", ",", "1918"], "label": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Platynota", "(", "genus", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Codington", "County", ",", "South", "Dakota"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Nez", "Perce", "National", "Forest"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["===", "2006-05-06", ":", "La", "Serena", "—", "Ovalle", "(", "110", "km", ")", "==="], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Sherkat-e", "Simorgh", ",", "Qazvin"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Nowe", ",", "Łódź", "Voivodeship"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Saint-Séverin", ",", "Mauricie", ",", "Quebec"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Port", "Elizabeth", ",", "South", "Africa"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Gangnam", ",", "South", "Korea"], "label": ["B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Glenwood", ",", "Nebraska"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Glossy", "ibis", ",", "''Plegadis", "falcinellus", "''"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["He", "was", "born", "in", "Derry", "and", "immigrated", "to", "New", "England", ",", "later", "moving", "to", "Truro", ",", "Nova", "Scotia", "in", "1761", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Chauvé", "(", "44038", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Eel", "River", "(", "California", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Philippine", "Sea", "Frontier"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Abdolabad", ",", "Delfan"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Aiguille", "du", "Tour"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Nowshiravan", ",", "Kermanshah"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Hough", "Springs", ",", "California"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Information", "taken", "from", "Cape", "Lookout", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "Kessleria", "alpicella", "''", "(", "Stainton", ",", "1851", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Deepwater", "big-eyed", "worm", "eel"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["*1973", "''North", "Face", "''", ",", "Wetterhorn", "Peak", ",", "San", "Juan", "Mountains", ",", "Colorado", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Seychelles", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["New", "York", "State", "Route", "17M"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Pioneer", "Valley", "Transit", "Authority", "(", "Springfield", ",", "Massachusetts", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Amarjit", "Chandan", "20th", "century"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Richard", "Shaw", "–", "1986"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Season", "'s", "Greetings", "from", "moe", ".", "''"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["Universal", "(", "Bren", "gun", ")", "carrier"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["South", "Coast", "railway", "line", ",", "New", "South", "Wales"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["''", "Runaround", "Sue", "''", "(", "Dion", "DiMucci", ",", "Ernie", "Maresca", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["Parkinson", "'s", "patients", ")", "."], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "If", "Loving", "You", "Is", "Wrong", "''"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["Commander", "of", "Torpedoboot", "''TA-20", "''"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["``", "Real", "Magic", "TV", "''"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["A", "Spanner", "in", "the", "Works", "''"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["National", "Highway", "24B", "(", "India", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["The", "Light", "Years", "''", ",", "released", "in", "1995", "and", "featuring", "more", "than", "twice", "as", "many", "tracks", ",", "is", "a", "much", "more", "comprehensive", "overview", "."], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["U.S.", "Route", "181"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Timeline", "of", "the", "Fukushima", "Daini", "nuclear", "accidents"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["It", "was", "instead", "covered", "by", "the", "1939-1945", "Star", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "Look", "of", "Love", "''"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["Saint", "Thomas", "Church", "(", "Manhattan", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Royal", "Australian", "Navy"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Greek", "American", "AA", "(", "4", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["One", "World", "Trade", "Center"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Way", "of", "the", "Blade", "''", "(", "2006", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Only", "Girl", "(", "In", "the", "World", ")", "(", "Rihanna", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "Killer", "''", "–", "Adamski", "feat", "."], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Iván", "Amaya", "–", "Apollon", "Limassol", "(", "2012", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["2014", "kidnapping", "and", "murder", "of", "Israeli", "teenagers"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Have", "a", "cumulative", "GPA", "of", "2.00", "or", "better"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["==", "''", "Stereochilus", "''", "=="], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["57th", "Infantry", "Regiment", "(", "Ottoman", "Empire", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Overview", "of", "the", "Karakoram", "Highway"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Lost", "to", "Detroit", "Spirits", "3-0"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["``", "Soul", "to", "Preach", "To", "''"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["Science", "Fiction", "Museum", "and", "Hall", "of", "Fame", ",", "Seattle", ",", "Washington", ",", "founded", "in", "2004", "."], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Permanent", "Court", "of", "Arbitration", "(", "PCA", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["On", "the", "Official", "Finnish", "Download", "Chart", ",", "the", "song", "peaked", "at", "number", "one", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Giants]]", "@", "San", "Juan", ",", "PR"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["In", "the", "15th", "century", "it", "was", "a", "personal", "property", "of", "the", "Odrowąż", "clan", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["He", "played", "previously", "for", "BK", "Mladá", "Boleslav", ",", "HC", "Hamé", "Zlín", ",", "HC", "Slovan", "Ústí", "nad", "Labem", "and", "SK", "Horácká", "Slavia", "Třebíč", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["*1983", ":", "Záhradná", "kaviareň", "''"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["List", "of", "regional", "mammals", "lists"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Home", "of", "Franklin", "D.", "Roosevelt", "National", "Historic", "Site"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Ohio", "Wesleyan", "University"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Attorney-General", "–", "'", "''", "Ralph", "Hanan", "''", "'", "."], "label": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Harry", "Judd", ",", "Dougie", "Poynter", ",", "Andrew", "Flintoff"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Björn", "at", "Haugi"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Pai", "Hsien-yung", "(", "born", "1937", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Dominique", "Wilkins", "(", "1979–1999", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["He", "was", "the", "son", "of", "Duwa", "Temür", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Assistant", "referees", ":", "'", "''"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["She", "was", "the", "daughter", "of", "William", "I", "de", "Cantilupe", "and", "Mazilia", "Braci", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["DJ", "Premier", "–", "producer"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Paul", "J.", "Weitz", "Karol", "J.", "Bobko", "Donald", "H.", "Peterson", "F.", "Story", "Musgrave"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["René", "Antoine", "Ferchault", "de", "Réaumur"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Rizzo", "the", "Rat", "as", "Wilhem", "Grimm"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Magda", "Francot", "(", "born", "1942", ")", ",", "painter"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Edward", "A.", "Gisburne"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["''Voiced", "by", ":", "Kayvan", "Novak", "''"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["Joe", "Morgan", "(", "1986–1987", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["*Produced", "by", "Carlos", "Santana", "and", "Clive", "Davis"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Pierre", "Du", "Moulin"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["**", "Jules", "Malou", "(", "1871–1878", ",", "1884", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["George", "Smathers", "-", "322,235", "(", "5.48", "%", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["The", "marriage", "was", "dissolved", "in", "1956", "and", "his", "ex-wife", "then", "married", "Sir", "Nigel", "Fisher", "MP", "in", "1956", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Edie", "Falco", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "Resting", "Place", "''", ",", "by", "David", "Campton"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Ice", "Cube", "feat", "."], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["François", "Dominique", "Séraphin"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Anastasia", "Martiusheva", "/", "Alexei", "Rogonov"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Pat", "Cash", "''", "(", "Semifinals", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Eva", "Mozes", "Kor"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Dwyane", "Wade", "(", "11", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Edward", "P.", "Costigan", "(", "D", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Julia", "Barretto", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Tatiana", "Volosozhar", "/", "Maxim", "Trankov", "Ksenia", "Stolbova", "/", "Fedor", "Klimov"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Waldo", "Williams", "(", "1904–1971", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["John", "III", "Sobieski"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Bobby", "Unser", "assumed", "the", "lead", "on", "lap", "182", ",", "with", "Mario", "Andretti", "second", "."], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": [":", "Stephen", "Bunting", "''", "(", "First", "round", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Chai", "Po", "Wa", "Qiao", "Yunping"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "With", "Billy", "Strayhorn", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Byron", "Mullens", "(", "12", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Tibor", "Pleiß", "-", "Utah", "Jazz"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["*Hospitalman", "Richard", "De", "Wert", "–", "5", "April", "1951", "(", "posthumously", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Gu", "Jiaming", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Jochen", "Schmid", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
]