[
{"text": ["Eslamabad", ",", "Haftkel"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Bradyrrhoa", "confiniella", "''", "Zeller", ",", "1848"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Gallatin", "National", "Forest", "(", "part", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Lake", "Township", ",", "Mercer", "County", ",", "Pennsylvania"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["It", "is", "located", "on", "the", "Arctic", "Circle", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["1967", "Intertoto", "Cup"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Coteau-du-Lac", ",", "Quebec"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["He", "lives", "in", "Pompano", "Beach", ",", "Florida", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "The", "Green", "Monkey", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Zırlankaya", ",", "Serik"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Buenavista", ",", "Bohol", "(", "barangay", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Gudarra", ",", "Western", "Australia"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["''", "Mamluk", "Sultanate", "of", "Egypt", "''", "'", "–", "Barsbay", "(", "1422–1437", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["It", "is", "found", "in", "Sumatra", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Jesup", ",", "Iowa"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Malagasy", "paradise", "flycatcher"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["''", "Eupithecia", "refertissima", "''"], "label": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Evans", "Bay", "is", "nearby", "."], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["São", "Sebastião", "da", "Vargem", "Alegre"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Saint", "Lucia", "black", "finch"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["**", "(", "6", ")", "Stanford", "37", ",", "Arizona", "0"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Born", "in", "Aurora", ",", "Minnesota", ",", "he", "grew", "up", "in", "nearby", "Eveleth", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Getaria", ",", "Gipuzkoa"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Hodgsons", "'s", "brown-toothed", "shrew"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Callahan", ",", "Florida"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["It", "is", "found", "in", "New", "South", "Wales", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Schloss", "Heiligenberg", "(", "Jugenheim", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Ran", "aground", "in", "the", "Salish", "Sea", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": [":241", "-", "(", "0-7", ")", "XXXXXX", "Larissa", "(", "and", "area", ")"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Sever", "do", "Vouga"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["It", "is", "operated", "by", "the", "Richmond", "Shire", "Council", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Local", "government", "in", "Northern", "Ireland"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Marabou", "stork", ",", "''Leptoptilos", "crumeniferus", "''"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["São", "Bartolomeu", "River"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["It", "is", "situated", "in", "the", "Huánuco", "Region", ",", "Huamalíes", "Province", ",", "Tantamayo", "District", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Dar", "Gol-e", "Seyyed", "Hasan"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Prusy", ",", "Opatów", "County"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "North", "Kalimantan", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Prime", "Minister", "of", "Greece"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Te", "Henga", "(", "Bethells", "Beach", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["It", "is", "part", "of", "the", "Cheyenne", ",", "Wyoming", "Metropolitan", "Statistical", "Area", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["He", "is", "from", "Andhra", "Pradesh", "in", "South", "India", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Long", "Island", "(", "Massachusetts", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Allendale", "Charter", "Township", ",", "Michigan"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Wey", "and", "Godalming", "Navigations"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Laryovo", ",", "Moscow", "Oblast"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Carleton", "(", "1834-1974", "electoral", "district", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["It", "is", "found", "in", "Austria", ",", "Switzerland", ",", "France", "and", "Italy", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Eden", ",", "North", "Carolina"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Sumner", "Township", ",", "Gratiot", "County"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["It", "includes", "the", "communities", "of", "Bellevue", ",", "Boya", ",", "Greenmount", ",", "Guildford", ",", "Hazelmere", ",", "Helena", "Valley", ",", "Jane", "Brook", ",", "Koongamia", ",", "Midland", ",", "Midvale", ",", "Stratton", ",", "Swan", "View", ",", "Viveash", ",", "Woodbridge", ",", "as", "well", "as", "parts", "of", "the", "communities", "of", "Darlington", ",", "Middle", "Swan", ",", "Red", "Hill", ",", "and", "South", "Guildford", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Mather", "Air", "Force", "Base", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["It", "was", "discovered", "in", "Oxyrhynchus", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["They", "wed", "on", "28", "April", "2007", "in", "their", "Malibu", "home", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Redwood", "National", "and", "State", "Parks"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Eversmann", "'s", "redstart"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Frąca", ",", "Gmina", "Osiek"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Watkins", "Glen", "International", "(", "5", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": [":", ":", ":", "''B.", "''", "ser.", "''Tetragonae", "''"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Pemba", "Island", ",", "Tanzania", "†", "[H]"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Edge", "Hill", ",", "Warwickshire"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Italy", ",", "New", "York"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Suli", "Daraq", ",", "Heris"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Woodlawn", ",", "Jefferson", "County", ",", "Illinois"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Daminah", "al-Gharbiyah", "1,012", "/", "(", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Communes", "of", "the", "Ariège", "department"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["2000–01", "Cymru", "Alliance"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["It", "is", "found", "in", "Guatemala", "and", "Mexico", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["File", ":", "Zlatorudne", "mlyny.jpg|Mills", "in", "Zlaté", "Hory"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["La", "Vernaz", "(", "74295", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Lagrange", ",", "Territoire", "de", "Belfort"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Chelleh", "Khaneh-ye", "Olya"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Couderay", "(", "town", ")", ",", "Wisconsin"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Jia", ",", "Iran"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["44-200", "to", "44-292", "–", "Rybnik"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Münster", "(", "Hesse", ",", "Germany", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Location", "in", "Lexington", ",", "Massachusetts"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["North", "East", "Scotland", "(", "Scottish", "Parliament", "electoral", "region", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Lone", "Wolf", "–", "$", "13,525"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Kırka", ",", "Eskişehir"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Koroška", "Vas", "na", "Pohorju"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["It", "is", "found", "in", "China", ",", "Laos", ",", "Myanmar", ",", "and", "Thailand", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Clay", "County", ",", "Kentucky"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Dalrymple", ",", "East", "Ayrshire"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["''Lazos", "''", "-", "Chile"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Cintheaux", "(", "14160", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Lamar", "County", ",", "Georgia"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["He", "was", "born", "in", "Yamaguchi", "Prefecture", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Cape", "May", ",", "New", "Jersey"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Wagoner", ",", "Oklahoma"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Historia", "Norwegiae", "''", "was", "written", "sometime", "between", "1160", "and", "1175", "CE", "in", "an", "unknown", "location", "."], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["``", "Hero", "''", "–", "Enrique", "Iglesias", "(", "November", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Days", "of", "Our", "Lives", "''"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["James", "Barry", "(", "disambiguation", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Armed", "Forces", "Bowl", ":", "Houston", "34", ",", "Air", "Force", "28"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["Hall", "Road", "Rangers", "F.C", "."], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Gardeners", "'", "Question", "Time"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Danbury", "Hatters", "'", "case"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Ubayd", "Allah", "al-Mahdi", "Billah", "–"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "So", "Alone", "''", "–", "(", "1978", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Toumaï", "Air", "Tchad"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Los", "Angeles", "Angels", "of", "Anaheim"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["**", "''", "Kendra", "on", "Top", "''", "(", "2012", ")"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["On", "5", "February", "2009", ",", "he", "earned", "his", "first", "call-up", "to", "the", "France", "under-21", "team", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "'Night", "Mother", "''", "–", "by", "Marsha", "Norman"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Beijing", "No.8", "High", "School"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["``", "Killing", "Me", "Softly", "with", "His", "Song", "''", "(", "Charles", "Fox", ",", "Norman", "Gimbel", ")", "-", "6:04"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["New", "York", "State", "Route", "172"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Defeated", "the", "(", "2", ")", "Milwaukee", "Bucks", ",", "4–1"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Cobo", "Hall", ",", "Detroit", ",", "Michigan", ",", "United", "States"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Xenosaga", ":", "Episode", "II", "''"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["Spanish", "conquest", "of", "Peru"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Major", "General", "Andrew", "Stewart", "(", "2004–2006", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Meet", "You", "at", "the", "Jazz", "Corner", "of", "the", "World"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Dunedin", ",", "New", "Zealand"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "A.F.C.", "Fylde", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["6", "August", "1846", "–", "18", "January", "1853", ":", "John", "Giles", "Price", "(", "1808–1857", ")"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["``", "Ai", "n't", "Too", "Proud", "to", "Beg", "''"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["GMA", "Network", "was", "also", "reportedly", "planning", "to", "bid", "but", "backed", "out", ";", "it", "however", "denied", "that", "they", "offered", "a", "bid", "."], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Charles", "Philip", "Haddon-Cave", ",", "former", "Financial", "Secretary", "of", "Hong", "Kong"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["``", "Every", "Day", "I", "Have", "the", "Blues", "''"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["John", "Kyme", "(", "disambiguation", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Nynäshamns", "IF", "18", "6", "3", "9", "46-38", "15"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "Look", "of", "Love", "''"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["3rd", "Battalion", "11th", "Marines"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["13", "Blues", "for", "Thirteen", "Moons", "''", "(", "2008", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["It", "runs", "from", "a", "connection", "with", "the", "Death", "Valley", "Fault", "Zone", "in", "the", "Amargosa", "Valley", "northward", "to", "a", "termination", "in", "the", "Fish", "Lake", "Valley", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "Shout", "It", "Out", "Loud", "''"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Gotlands", "nation", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Jodhpur", "National", "University"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["''", "Samurai", "7", "''"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["I", "Am", "the", "Greatest", ":", "The", "Adventures", "of", "Muhammad", "Ali"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["53d", "Wing", "(", "53", "WG", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["The", "attack", "caught", "the", "US", "8th", "Cavalry", "Regiment", "unprepared", "at", "Sangju", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Julie", "Is", "Her", "Name", ",", "Volume", "II", "''", "–", "Julie", "London"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["The", "8th", "Parliament", "continues", "."], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["New", "York", "Times", ",", "''", "June", "20", ",", "2007", "."], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Kong", ":", "The", "Animated", "Series", "''"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["Members", "elected", "to", "the", "2nd", "Scottish", "Parliament"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Château", "de", "Champs-sur-Marne"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["``", "Chasing", "Pavements", "''", "—", "Adele"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER"]},
{"text": ["``", "Something", "About", "the", "Way", "You", "Look", "Tonight", "/", "Candle", "in", "the", "Wind", "1997", "''"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["Internal", "Revenue", "Service"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Sex", "and", "the", "City", "''"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "The", "Jean", "Genie", "''", "–", "David", "Bowie"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["On", "19", "May", "2010", ",", "AC", "/", "DC", "was", "there", "for", "their", "Black", "Ice", "World", "Tour"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["National", "University", "of", "the", "South"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Battle", "Creek", "Revolution"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Islands", "of", "South", "Korea"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Tyranny", "(", "For", "You", ")", "''"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["''", "DragonflyTV", "''", "(", "January", "19", ",", "2002–January", "31", ",", "2009", ";", "June", "1", ",", "2014-August", "24", ",", "2014", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["I", "Will", "Say", "Goodbye", "''"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["**", "The", "Platinum", "Collection", "''", "(", "2006", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Drama", "City", "''", "``", "낙타씨의", "행방불명", "''"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["*2004", ":", "Be", "Here", "''", "by", "Keith", "Urban"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["US", "1A", "''", "–", "Port", "Chester", ",", "New", "York"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["İstanbulspor", "A.Ş", "."], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["''", "PBA", "on", "Fox", "Sports", "''", "(", "2013-present", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["and", "was", "educated", "at", "Westminster", "School", "and", "Brasenose", "College", ",", "Oxford", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["San", "Pasqual", "Battlefield", "State", "Historic", "Park"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["West", "Virginia", "Route", "67"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Corby", "Town", "F.C", "."], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["University", "of", "Arkansas"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Sold", "in", "1983", "to", "Alan", "Keef", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["Hertha", "BSC", "Berlin", "(", "5", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["**", "Howard", "University", "founded", "."], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["``", "The", "Seed", "(", "2.0", ")", "''"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["Gieronia", "(", "based", "on", "Starbem", "Gyeron", "from", "Ultraseven", "''", ")"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["GMA", "Films", "and", "Viva", "Films"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["SpongeBob", "SquarePants", "(", "season", "7", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["''", "Gideon", "'s", "Crossing", "''", "(", "2000–2001", ")"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Shortly", "after", ",", "it", "rejected", "the", "Fourteenth", "Amendment", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["Sine", "loco", "''", ",", "a", "term", "used", "in", "bibliographies", "to", "indicate", "that", "the", "place", "of", "publication", "of", "a", "document", "is", "unknown"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "With", "Jimmy", "Bruno", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Mark", "Sheppard", "as", "Romo", "Lampkin"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["It", "is", "currently", "owned", "by", "the", "singer", "Enya", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O"]},
{"text": [";", "Written", "by", "Dennis", "Potter"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Vicente", "Fernández", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Wiffi", "Smith", "won", "the", "event", "."], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Chip", "'n", "Dale", "Rescue", "Rangers", "''"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Ernests", "Gulbis", "[24]", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "'", "''", "Nikita", "Lobintsev", "(", "1:45.10", ")", "Mikhail", "Polischuk", "(", "1:45.42", ")", "Danila", "Izotov", "(", "1:44.48", ")", "Alexander", "Sukhorukov", "(", "1:44.15", ")"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Allan", "Williams", "(", "politician", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Scott", "Sharp", "Johannes", "van", "Overbeek"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Nelson", "Piquet", ",", "Jr", ".", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Maurice", "Boitel", "(", "1919–2007", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Jelle", "Klaasen", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Cristian", "Chagas", "Tarouco"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["``", "Yùjiàn", "''", "(", "遇見", "``", "Meet", "''", ")", "(", "originally", "by", "Stefanie", "Sun", ")"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["Zofia", "Czartoryska", "(", "1778–1837", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Arslanmyrat", "Amanow", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Max", "von", "Sydow", "as", "The", "Father"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["*22", "January", "1947", "–", "22", "October", "1947", ":", "François", "Mitterrand"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Benny", "Dollo", "(", "''Interim", "Coach", "''", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Steven", "van", "Herwijck"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Mike", "Donlin", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Stuart", "Chandler", ",", "a", "character", "on", "All", "My", "Children", "''", "played", "by", "David", "Canary"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Radu", "Beligan", "(", "2008", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Reed", "Smoot", "(", "R-UT", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Albert", "Pujols", "[2]", "(", "2006", ",", "2010", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Jerome", "F.", "Donovan", "(", "D", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Selmir", "dos", "Santos", "Bezerra"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Jung", "Joon-young", "(", "feat", "."], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Joaquim", "Pinto", "as", "himself"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Andrex", "(", "actor", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Edgar", "Carrasco", "Arteaga", "(", "1946-present", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Ken", "Piesse", "(", "2004", ")", "."], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Leelavathi", "as", "Padtragiri", "'s", "wife"], "label": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Reggie", "Burrell", "–", "production"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["William", "J.", "P.", "MacMillan", "''"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["The", "founder", "Mustafa", "Kemal", "Atatürk", "died", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Crystal", "Snow", "Jenne"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Speculated", "names", "of", "Prithviraj", "Sukumaran", "and", "Dulquer", "Salmaan", "surfaced", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["1944", "Ernest", "W.", "Goodpasture"], "label": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["José", "Zúñiga", "(", "artist", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Jacques", "Cousteau", "and", "Louis", "Malle"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Pedro", "Álvarez", "Castelló"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Thomas", "Witlam", "Atkinson", "(", "1799–1861", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Dana", "Andrews", ",", "Richard", "Conte"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Adrian", "Winter", ",", "Orlando", "City"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Alberto", "Pérez", "(", "musician", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Sparsh", "Khanchandani", "-", "Uttran", "''", "as", "Ichchha"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Louis", "de", "Rouvroy", ",", "duc", "de", "Saint-Simon"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Julie", "Delpy", "/", "Daniel", "Brühl"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": [")", "''", "and", "Cee-Lo", "Green", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["border", "'", "''", "Séamus", "Harnedy"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Pink", "(", "8", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["It", "was", "described", "by", "Walker", "in", "1859", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Ouran", "High", "School", "Host", "Club"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["He", "became", "friends", "with", "one", "of", "his", "fellow", "officers", "Charles", "Grey", "whose", "career", "he", "later", "assisted", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Mark", "Selby", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["James", "Fraser", "Forbes"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Bruce", "Beresford", "(", "Non-Jew", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["The", "first", "3", "songs", "as", "PopCrush", "97.1", "were", "Pitbull", "/", "Christina", "Aguilera", "'s", "Feel", "This", "Moment", "''", ",", "Justin", "Timberlake", "'s", "Mirrors", "''", ",", "and", "Rihanna", "'s", "Umbrella", "''", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Brian", "McKnight", "-", "``", "Still", "''"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Andre", "Miller", "(", "6", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Karl", "Benjamin", "(", "December", "29", ",", "1925", "–", "July", "26", ",", "2012", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["LeBron", "James", "(", "34", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Anne", "Geneviève", "de", "Bourbon", "(", "1619–1679", ")", ",", "married", "to", "Henri", "II", "d'Orléans", ",", "Duke", "of", "Longueville"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Patriarch", "Theophilos", "III", "of", "Jerusalem"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Daniel", "Naborowski", "(", "1573–1640", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Marsilius", "of", "Padua", "(", "1275-1342", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Terry", "Cummings", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Two", "locations", "have", "been", "suggested", ",", "one", "by", "Eric", "Birley", "in", "1961", ","], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Thisara", "Perera", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["It", "starred", "Angus", "Deayton", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["Rainier", "III", ",", "Prince", "of", "Monaco"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Jennifer", "Jones", ",", "Gina", "Lollobrigida"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": [":", "*Character", "Basis", ":", "Xun", "Yu"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Referee", ":", "'", "''", "Red", "Cashion"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Francisco", "Clavet", "''", "'", "7–5", ",", "6–1", ",", "6–1"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Dominic", "Purcell", "as", "Lincoln", "Burrows"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Ozzy", "Osbourne", "–", "Time", "After", "Time"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["David", "Weir", "(", "writer", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["1952", ",", "Gertrude", "Melville", "(", "ALP", ")"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "Nikita", "Koloff", "''", "'", "''"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Dale", "Robertson", ",", "Anne", "Francis"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Bohdan", "Ulihrach", "''", "(", "First", "Round", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Pei", ",", "Songzhi", "."], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["John", "Morse", "(", "British", "politician", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Tyler", "Simpson", "DF", "28.08.1985"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Casgrain", ",", "Henri-Raymond", "(", "1895", ")", "."], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Augusto", "Palacios", "(", "1992–94", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "With", "Ry", "Cooder", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Andreas", "Krause", "(", "footballer", ",", "born", "1967", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Bob", "Ryan", "(", "mayor", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Horace", "B.", "Strait"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Hamdan", "bin", "Mubarak", "Al", "Nahyan"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Jane", "Powell", ",", "Cliff", "Robertson"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["Charles", "Kirkhoven", ",", "1st", "Earl", "of", "Bellomont", "(", "died", "1683", ")"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
]