[
{"text": ["Ramulispora", "acuformis", "''", "[anamorph]"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Republic", "of", "Venice"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Sandstone", ",", "West", "Virginia"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["It", "is", "found", "in", "Guyana", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Ústí", "(", "Vsetín", "District", ")"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Plumerville", ",", "Arkansas", "–", "$", "13,968"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["It", "is", "found", "in", "Queensland", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["The", "species", "can", "be", "found", "on", "Lake", "Superior", ",", "Marquette", ",", "Michigan", "as", "well", "as", "Laniel", ",", "Quebec", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["Olustee", ",", "Oklahoma"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC"]},
{"text": ["Sajid", "dynasty", "(", "889", "/", "890–929", ")", "of", "Sogdian", "origin"], "label": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]},
{"text": ["**", "''", "Kingdom", "of", "Gwent", "''", "'", "–", "Edwyn", "ap", "Gwriad", "(", "1015–1045", ")"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["**", "''", "Rock", "and", "Roll", "Part", "2", "''", "by", "Gary", "Glitter", "(", "ECW", ")"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]},
{"text": ["KIMA", ":", "Uncle", "Jimmy", "'s", "Clubhouse", "''", "(", "Jim", "Nolan", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["SpongeBob", "SquarePants", "(", "season", "7", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["New", "York", "State", "Route", "237"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Lincoln", "University", "(", "New", "Zealand", ")"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["11th", "Regiment", "Kentucky", "Volunteer", "Cavalry"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["Tokyo", "Bay", "Aqua-Line", "completed", "in", "1997"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Children", "'s", "Museum", "of", "Houston"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]},
{"text": ["''", "'", "''", "Keeping", "Up", "with", "the", "Kardashians", "''", "'", "''"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Phoenix", "''", "(", "1984", ")", "1"], "label": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["David", "Guetta", "ft.", "Zara", "Larsson"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["The", "release", "features", "Mohsen", "Namjoo", "as", "guest", "singer", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Vânia", "Cristina", "Martins"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["''", "December", "4", "''", "–", "The", "First", "Hundred", "Years"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER"]},
{"text": ["'", "''", "With", "Yuka", "Honda", "''", "'"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Vladimir", "Arsenyev", "–", "Dersu", "Uzala", "''"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]},
{"text": ["David", "and", "Simon", "Reuben", "-", "Businessmen", "."], "label": ["B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Noel", "Howlett", "-", "Lawyer"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]},
{"text": ["Vittorio", "Brambilla", "''", "Jacques", "Laffite"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
]